<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Hashtagdateme</title>
  <generator uri="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    <icon>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/apple-touch-icon-precomposed.png</icon>
  <subtitle></subtitle>
  <link href="http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <updated>2017-01-11T10:48:55+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name></name>
    <uri>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/</uri>
    
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <title>How to Take the Perfect Selfie for Your Dating Profile</title>
    <link href="http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/dating/how-to-take-the-perfect-selfie-for-your-dating-profile/"/>
    <updated>2016-11-26T12:32:38+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/dating/how-to-take-the-perfect-selfie-for-your-dating-profile</id>
    <author>
      <name></name>
      <uri>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/</uri>
      
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      
      &lt;p&gt;Find your best angle &amp;ndash; take selfies using all angles to find the angle that best accentuates your features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use different poses to get your best selfie. Use a genuine smile &amp;ndash; try to think about something that makes you happy, nobody likes a fake smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have the best lighting &amp;ndash; you can use a bedroom lamp, or bright light even consider natural daylight for that authentic look. Stay away from fluorescent lights as they bring out imperfections. The ideal lighting for looking good in photos is indirect sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using filters correctly - don&amp;rsquo;t over filter your selfie you want to appear how you look in person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose a surrounding carefully &amp;ndash; choose a surrounding that makes you feel comfortable as you take your selfie, you don&amp;rsquo;t want to take a selfie with a dumpster behind you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear appropriate clothing &amp;ndash; if you&amp;rsquo;re not at the beach on holiday you don&amp;rsquo;t want to wear a bikini. Find something that matches your personality, whether it&amp;rsquo;s conservative, casual, trendy or colorful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Front face or back camera selfie &amp;ndash; test each side for best selfie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try to relax &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s just a selfie, don&amp;rsquo;t overthink it and keep it simple.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tips for Dating</title>
    <link href="http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/dating/tips-for-dating/"/>
    <updated>2016-11-14T12:28:42+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/dating/tips-for-dating</id>
    <author>
      <name></name>
      <uri>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/</uri>
      
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      
      &lt;p&gt;Here are a few tips to get you started on having a successful date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Bringing up topics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not bring up topics you are not willing to talk about more in details. If you are engaging in a conversation the worst thing to do is bring up a topic you have no desire to elaborate on. Your date would wonder why bring up a topic and might think you have something to hide which will give you the appearance of being dishonest. Only talk about topics you are interested in talking about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never talk about your ex&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody wants to feel like they are being compared to somebody else. It would also give the impression that you have not moved on. If you&amp;rsquo;re hoping for a second date then definitely avoid talking about your ex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be yourself &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best policy in life is never be fake and this doesn&amp;rsquo;t apply only in the world of dating. In general always be yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Make eye contact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always make eye contact this way your date will know you are interested and a great way to establish a connection. It&amp;rsquo;s well known that the eyes are the window to the soul who knows you might find your soul mate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Smile&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smile when appropriate, try not to fake a smile it really doesn&amp;rsquo;t look attractive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Listen&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s always good to listen carefully so you can seamlessly carry on conversation and ask questions. A good conversation is like a good tennis game, however keep your ears on the ball and listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Chivalry is still alive&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Men should try to adopt being chivalrous at their best. A small gesture like holding the door open or pulling out the chair makes a lady feel special. As for the ladies don&amp;rsquo;t expect too much chivalry from your knight in shining armor as this can lead to quick judgment or disappointment but just a little chivalry is like the icing on the cake, it&amp;rsquo;s very sweet so don&amp;rsquo;t expect too much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Stay positive&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last thing a date wants to hear is negative comments about work colleagues, what&amp;rsquo;s happening in your life and all things drama. Leave your baggage aside as this could easily push a date away from another date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Pick a great location&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are going to pick a location for a date think about what you are both interested in so that you can determine what place would best suit both parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Splitting the bill&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s good to at least offer to split the bill. Your date would appreciate this and won&amp;rsquo;t feel you were just looking for a free meal and makes a good impression.&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hashtagging Your Sexual Orientation</title>
    <link href="http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/dating/hashtagging-your-sexual-orientation/"/>
    <updated>2016-11-11T12:31:19+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/dating/hashtagging-your-sexual-orientation</id>
    <author>
      <name></name>
      <uri>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/</uri>
      
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      
      &lt;p&gt;Hashtagdateme is not only for people who are heterosexual but for all types of orientation. If you are a sassy young lady looking for an even sassier young lady just use #lesbian #homosexual. Then there&amp;rsquo;s #gay #bisexual whichever best describes your orientation to help you find that perfect match.&lt;/p&gt;


    </content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Welcome to Hashtagdateme</title>
    <link href="http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/hashtagdateme/welcome-to-hashtagdateme/"/>
    <updated>2016-11-04T18:29:06+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/hashtagdateme/welcome-to-hashtagdateme</id>
    <author>
      <name></name>
      <uri>http://blog.hashtagdateme.com/</uri>
      
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      
      &lt;p&gt;Welcome to Hashtagdateme!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is the official launch day of Hashtagdateme dating app now available to download on the App Store and Google Play Store . If you have used a dating service where matches were simply based on just looks or couldn&amp;rsquo;t match according to your interest then Hashtagdateme is for you. At hashtagdateme there are no endless forms to fill, with a simple easy registration you could be on your way to finding the perfect date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We simplify the process of finding a person using our unique hashtag system. Simply add hashtags about yourself and in a seperate box you can add hashtags of what you are looking for in your date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not sure what hashtags to use, here are some ideas:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#fun #cool #tall #handsome #doctor #explorer #blueeyes #brunette #friendly #caring #romantic #adventurous #spontaneous #casualdating #soulmate #healthy #foodie #dance #music #artistic #freespirited #traveler #hiking #camping #caucasian #tanned #lawyer #teacher #beautician #entrepreneur #independent #commitment #lovespets #sporty #petite #blonde #slim #mediumbuild #redhead #bigeyes #cute #lovelysmile #goodteeth #vegetarian #feminist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>